Kettle and Idols
Kettle and Idol
Now, and the third.
Shut up and be loud
This is really said by the members and others,
When someone sings a phrase of a song,
When someone sings a phrase of a song, they cut out a part of the song and continue singing it forever.
Yes, yes, yes.
And often unconsciously,
Rina, you're singing that again," I am often told,
When I get into it, it's very noisy.
They say, "That's enough, that's enough.
There are some amazing people.
That's right.
There are people who sing during that period all the time.
And they only sing that phrase,
So many people say, "That's enough.
That's right.
When they get hooked, they are very noisy.
Also, recently, I've been thinking about food,
Yuzu, banana juice, and baby sponge cakes,
They are quite addicted to them, aren't they?
Yes, they are. There are a lot of them,
Once they get hooked, they usually stay hooked,
They even recommend them to their friends,
I think people who are not interested in it are probably annoyed by it.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
The thing I have been most addicted to so far is....
Hamburgers.
I guess I've been addicted to hamburgers for a long time.
That was when I was in high school,
I ate hamburgers about five times a week,
It's crazy, isn't it?
This is serious.
In high school, you eat a lot, don't you?
I ate a lot.
I eat in the morning, eat in the morning when I get to school, eat for lunch, eat after school,
After lunch, after school,
I ate snacks, ate at night, and ate dinner at night,
That's right.
At the end of the school day, we would eat hamburgers at the break.
That's also a gathering?
Yes, that's right.
The school cafeteria?
No, not the cafeteria, but outside.
Hamburgers outside?
At a restaurant or something.
Oh, really?
That's right.
But even homosexuals have an image of the proposal.
Yes, that's right.
But I have lost a lot of weight since I was in high school.
You have lost a lot of weight?
Yes, I have lost a lot of weight.
I sweat for all kinds of people in the world.
We ate hamburgers at the meeting.
Yes, that's right.
We had hamburgers for lunch and then hamburgers at night.
We ate hamburgers for lunch and hamburgers for dinner.
I loved it.
Hands, feet, and ears, too.
I'm grateful to my parents.
That's right.
I see.
You love hamburgers?
I love hamburgers.
Do you have a favorite place?
Wow, it's hard to decide.
Oh, it's not so easy.
Yes, it is.
There are a lot of raw hamburgers these days.
Yes, there are.
Inside, right?
The skin is a little rough and rare.
But he likes the fresh hamburger steak the best.
It can only be found in Shizuoka.
I like the fact that you can't get there quickly and the difference in the center of gravity.
That's for sure.
That's right.
I'm already captivated by it.
There is also a hamburger restaurant in Shinjuku that I really want to go to,
I have tried twice, and both times I couldn't get in.
The restaurant was too crowded.
Is there such a hamburger restaurant?
Yes, there is.
I was thinking of going there for the third time.
What kind of hamburgers are they?
It's a hamburger steak restaurant that is popular nowadays, and the hamburgers are thick and almost raw.
I would love to hear what you think if you go there.
I would love to go there.
I heard that Rina-san is very picky when it comes to hamburgers.
Thank you very much.
You may not know that.
It's true that this might be another story that I don't get a chance to talk about.
This program was provided by Mr. Guggel, Mr. Keisuke, Mr. Acky, Mr. Mamono, and Ms. Renren.
Thank you all very much.
What a fun last show!